Thanks, Rado. Now that we know the distinct advantages of using a list view,
we can use a list view to display the list of weather forecasts in our app.
Now, which file in the layout folder should we modify to accomplish this?
Well, we want to add the list view directly to the fragment. If you open up
the fragment_main.xml file, you'll notice that the layout includes a relative
layout as the parent view, as well as a child TextView. Modify this file so that
we show a ListView instead of a TextView and assign it an ID ListViewForecast so
we can reference it later. Also, since this layout only contains one child's
view, it would be more efficient to actually switch to a FrameLayout instead of
a RelativeLayout. After you make the changes, compile and
run your app. You'll be a little underwhelmed with the blank screen, but
that's okay. That's because we haven't populated the list view with data yet,
and that will come in a later step. Check the box when you're done.